The upstarts of the great
pirate era have gained a
momentum that not even the world
government is prepared for.
During this exciting age,
there's one man standing at the
epicenter of everyone's attention.
Monkey D.
Luffy and his crew, the Straw Hats.
In order to stay ahead of these
turbulent times, Every four years,
50 global leaders hold a world
summit in the Holy Land of Marijua.
This event, known as the
Reverie, is about to begin.
The fate of the world is about
to take a dramatic new turn.
I'm so hungry.
Hmm?
What's this junk?
Whoa, where did you get that? Uh-uh.
They wound up in my pocket somehow.
Holy crap, is it real? Why?
What is it anyway?
Don't you remember?
Jeremiah used them to do
those cool transformations.
Whoa, so that's it.
Let me give that thing a quick spin.
I'm going before you.
Uh, Sponji?
I'm going to chuck this hunk of garbage.
Ah!
Don't throw it away!
If you do, I'm going to dive to
the bottom of the sea to find it!
Good luck with that.
You can't swim.
It was in my pocket, so if you don't
want it, just give it back to me instead!
I'll gladly take it off
your hands! Get lost.
I am rather curious as to how it
wandered into Luffy's pockets.
Must have been Niji.
He probably did it to piss me off.
If I'm gonna get stronger,
I won't do it by relying on this
thing or some technological crap.
Run it down, please!
Why is this the power of mankind itself?
What do you guys want it for?
If you let us put the rave suit on!
Maybe we can shoot laser beams!
What, are you guys ten years old?
Besides, Frankie's got enough lasers and
crap for the whole crew. No, sweetie!
What was that?
Did you insult science?
Oh, tell me!
Why perish the thought?
I think science is lovely.
My sorcerer's climate act
was made from atmospheric
science and the craftsmanship
of our own new sub-general.
Now, out!
I'm really loving life in that baton.
Zeus, you actually tagged along?
I can't believe you chose your
stomach over loyalty to Big Mom.
He's quite the useful servant, isn't he?
He's your what, Nami?
Oh, yeah?
Zeus,
just so you know, I've been Nami's devoted
servant long before you showed up, okay?
I mean, that's cute and all,
but I get to live inside her
baton, which never leaves her side.
Sanji, you're yelling at
a massive water vapor.
Chirma, let's power up!
Where the heck's my cool
suit? Stop your crying.
I guess the thing only
works when you do it, huh?
Show us how it's done. Shut up.
I'm not part of that goon squad. No rules.
Don't say the word
Vinsmoke or Germa either.
They're officially off limits
any time you're around me.
Vinsmoke?
Let go of me, you dumbasses!
Guys, the paper's here!
Is there any coverage about
us crushing the wedding?
Let's see.
Luffy's on the front page!
What about Jinbei?
Does it say if he made it out okay, or?
Um, Jinbei, Jinbei.
No, I don't see anything.
It says Luffy, Sanji, Jinbei, and
Buggy attempted to assassinate Big Mom.
And you, Tia, were the mastermind.
Mastermind?
Look, Sanji! Hmm?
My bounty increased to
330 million berries?
No friggin' way! Huh?
What's Mosshead sitting at?
That should put him right below you now.
He has a 320 million bounty.
Hell yeah!
In your face, jackass!
It's just a number, don't flip out.
And they change it from alive
only back to dead or alive!
Sanji?
What's the matter?
My name.
Huh?
It changed to Vinsmoke Sanji.
Damn it!
It was only increased because
of my family's reputation.
Sanji, buddy?
You gonna be all right?
It's somehow even gloomier over there!
Luffy, what's the problem?
Meanwhile, everyone is abuzz
about the upcoming reverie,
a conference made up of
all the world's leaders.
It takes place in the holy land of
Marijoire once every four years.
This is Fishman Island, located
10,000 meters below sea level.
It's home of the Ryugu Kingdom.
They did it, Jamon.
Jinbei has finally joined Luffy's crew.
It's hard to believe that the two of
them picked a fight with Big Mom herself.
Do you suppose they were all
able to escape on the same ship?
I certainly hope so, la-ti-do!
Surely they did.
In the article, it mentions
that Big Mom is furious.
I don't think Big Mom will be so
keen to protect our country anymore.
We'll have to see if Straw Hat will do it.
Don't leave yet, father!
Shirahoshi!
I'm coming with you, to the reverie.
If I go, Luffy won't be able to pick
on me for being a Secret cat anymore.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
I was hoping you would find the courage.
All right, are you ready?
Uh-huh.
Though the meeting of world
leaders is certainly big news,
word of Luffy's bold adventure seemed
to be the only thing on anyone's mind.
The story about a young
pirate who took a stand
against the untouchable
Emperor of the Sea,
Big Mom,
thrills all who hear it across the world.
The newspaper states,
Sources report that Straw Hat
Luffy is already in control of
seven powerful pirate crews that
he's recruited along the way.
This makes him the captain
of a fleet that has
a combined total of over
5,000 fearsome pirates.
He's not only the sworn brother
of the late ace, but also Sabo,
second in command of
the Revolutionary Army.
His natural magnetism and
leadership skills have
drawn the evil army Germa
Double Six to his side,
along with the Sun Pirates and
the Fire Tank Pirates as well.
His plan to destroy Big
Mom's castle can only
be seen as a work of strategic brilliance.
Additionally, he defeated her highest-ranked
officers with sheer strength alone.
The outcome of this battle
clearly confirms that
Straw Hatluffy is a force
to be reckoned with.
And the last slide of the
article makes a bold statement.
The fifth emperor of the sea has emerged.
Are you kidding?
What's this fifth emperor bullcrap?
The press must have lost
their damn minds giving
such a lavish title to a
little upstart like him.
fleet admiral we have a
problem the kingdom of
Lulusia ship that was
in route to the reverie
has been attacked by pirates the king was
unharmed but princess
Comane has been kidnapped
what was the point of an armed escort
jack
It's all about Lucy yes
I saw okay I'm so proud
that's our captain Luffy
Land is even more famous
now and it's kind of cool
out a newspaper mentions
all of us too don't forget
once we When we arrive, Leo,
you cannot bring up such matters. Huh?
Why can't we, though?
It's quite simple.
We owe a great debt to the Straw Hats,
but the government sees
them in a different way.
Let's keep that in mind.
Oh, you're right.
They are pirates.
Straw Hat Luffy is
considered a dangerous man.
Best to avoid trouble.
I suppose so.
Oh, yeah, I should show this to Viola.
Hey, wait for us!
There's no mistaking it
those ships are from the
Dressrosa and Prodents kingdoms
and not a marine in sight.
Oh
It's Princess Viola.
She's just as stunning as they say,
the girl she's with is
also a royal family member.
I think if we can kidnap these two.
I wonder how much we get for them
Agreed Princess Comane
This is why I love nabbing royalty.
Hold out for a few more.
Let's make that ransom real hefty.
Those suckers can't spot us, they can't
catch us, and they'll never see us coming.
Gentlemen, I love this submarine.
Sink them. Roger.
Good luck guarding
against a torpedo. Ha-ha!
Huh?
Oh no!
An attack!
Ready the cannon! Yes, sir!
Not necessary.
Glad I made it in time.
You're all safe now.
Are you a Marine a captain from HQ?
I'm Koby did it miss the target?
There's no way
Your parties are from
dress Rosa and Prodence
isn't that correct a long
way you must be tired Huh?
What just happened? Oh, my.
Where did you come from?
I was patrolling on that Navy ship.
You know, you folks were being stalked
by some pirates just now. Underwater.
Under the surface?
Was it a torpedo?
I'm sure Gladly missed us. Me too.
El Meppo, how goes it?
We've got the pirates under control.
The Lulusia princess Comane is fine.
Roast these bastards on a skewer!
You'll suffer! Just wait. You monsters?
Let's calm down.
We'll handle them easy now.
I still don't get how your observation.
Haki is so in tune.
Kobe crazy!
I wasn't able to sense the torpedo at all.
A submarine—you have to be
careful with pirates these days.
That was a bit too close.
You there?
The
famous captain covey, I presume.
So is he the one from rocky port?
So you were the marine from the incident?
The one perpetrated by trafalgar
law of the worst generation!
Incredible this hero
protected all those people.
Oh, I'm hardly a hero.
It's nothing.
So you're not only daring
but you're humble too!
Wow, this guy looks tough.
What a fine lad.
If only he could take a compliment.
Thank you, thanks Luffy!
No way!
Oh sorry, I mean I just noticed the headline
in the newspaper you're holding here.
Take it.
No, no. Well?
well Well, I mean, if you don't mind.
The fifth emperor of the sea has emerged.
I'm so proud of him.
He's so cool.
He keeps reaching higher and higher.
Uh, hey.
Every time I see you in the
newspaper, I think back to that day.
Captain Colby, what are you doing?
Come on back.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Okay, let's go.
We're nearly to New Marine Ford.
The Navy would be happy to escort
you the rest of the way there.
Good. Let's go.
Hey.
What is it?
Lucy's your friend, isn't he?
Kobe, you like Luffy Land?
Nuh—uh, he's a foe.
Yeah, right.
Don't
worry, we won't tell.
I think we should have a little talk.
I'm a Navy officer, and
I need to get going.
But
you looked so happy when
you were reading the paper.
paper
That's because I, uh...
Come on, let's talk.
No, please stop.
Oh, Luffy Lund's in this article, too.
Yes, so you are his friend.
Damn my bounty only increased because of
Jerema's bad rep that takes
all the fun out of it.
Hey, are you okay?
Just look, my bounty's gone down.
You see, it's 150 million.
Are you sure?
Wasn't it 500 a while back?
That went down by a whole lot.
It's even lower than it was two years ago.
How is that possible?
Did you do something wrong, perhaps?
Isn't that backwards?
Oh, yes, you're right.
No biggie.
Less people will be after your head now.
Nami, how could you say that?
Luffy is our captain.
It could harm our prestige.
Damn it! Why?!
Ready the cannons!
And fire!
Let's go!
Have anything left by down!
What the hell is the Navy doing?
I thought they were here to protect us.
You'll pay for destroying our ship.
Take him out!
Momohahaha!
The Navy's just a joke.
Lucky us!
The Lucia king is away for the reverie,
and he took all his best soldiers with him.
For pirates like me, an unguarded country
like this is ripe for the picking.
Now listen up and listen well.
Have you ever heard of the
Emperor of the Sea, Blackbeard?
I work under him, and I've
taken the name Peachbeard.
You would do well to remember it.
Fear, Blackbeard!
All right, gentlemen,
let's start loading up the ships
and make our leader proud, shall we?
Gotcha, now empty those pockets.
Okay, just get off of me.
It's no use trying to get away.
We'll burn this whole place down.
Can you stand?
Let's get you out of here.
Hey, you better not let
that girl escape, huh?
Not so fast.
What's that you got there, missy?
Now,
what in the world could be so precious that
you would dare try and hide it from me?
Sorry, sir. Huh?
Is that milk?
I thought it would be money.
No big deal.
I'll take it anyway.
Please, mister.
This is for the children of the village.
Ah, shut up!
You're really willing to
risk your life for some milk?
Please give it back to me. I beg of you.
It's not much, but we need it.
Huh?
Why don't you hand over your money, too?
I don't have any.
I bet you have your
heavenly tribute, though.
Yes,
but the heavenly tribute
is what we have to
pay to the king and the Celestial Dragons.
We're barely getting by as is.
It takes every last berry
we can scrape together.
If we can't pay the heavenly
tribute, we'll be put to death.
What a shame.
Your king sounds terrible.
I guess I have no choice.
You fellas know what to do.
Rip this town apart and find
where they hid the money!
It's gotta be somewhere!
We're gonna be rich!
No, don't!
Tell us, where's the tribute stashed away?
Just leave us alone!
Our town has nothing!
Please don't take this money!
It's all I have!
Get your grubby hands off!
Someone help!
You wouldn't have gotten beaten if
you had given us what we wanted!
Kill everyone who disobeys!
We've suffered enough!
Please leave our people alone! Huh?
Shut your trap!
Morley, let's do this. Huh?
And just who the hell are you?
Why is the ground shaking?
Something is coming up from the street!
What the hell?
Why is a huge-ass trident here?
Huh?
Is that a giant?
One, two, one, two, one,
two, one, two, one, two!
What the hell was this
huge guy doing underground?
That's, uh, some outfit man.
Uh, why is he wearing a mini skirt?
Don't be a creep.
Watch where you're looking.
Hmm.
Hey, buddy, my eyes are up here.
If you're that into me,
then just say it, bro.
Where did you get that idea?
Those are some mighty
tall accusations there.
I've had enough of you.
Just shoot this guy.
You little boys should leave me alone.
So, since when do giants live underground?
I've never seen one before.
I wonder who this guy is.
Big ol' meanies like you will be punished!
Let's go!
How is this guy pushing the
root around like it's clay?
Don't back down!
It's only a Devil Fruit!
He's so tough.
So, what do you want to do?
Use submissive pieces of trash.
Hey, that's rude.
What do you suggest we do?
Excuse me?
Who are you people and what
do you want with our town?
Oh my!
Now, now, Morley!
Don't have all the fun without me!
What do you want?
Wait a sec, I've got some
newly invented weapons to try!
What, you run out ahead, huh?
Who the hell are these circus monkeys?
Why's the murder of crows here?
Captain, look, someone's on the roof.
What?
Why are the birds gathering up?
How dare you attempt to harm the innocent?
Oh!
Captain Peachbeard, sir!
They shouldn't be here!
They're supposed to be
scared across the world!
They're the four captains
of the Revolutionary Army!
Wait! No, wait!
They're what?!
Knock it off!
You're still staring!
Are you scared yet, scumbag?
I'm dying to try my new weapons on you!
We won't allow you to do as you please.
Revolutionaries?
Are they here to help?
Heee-haw!
Strawboy really is
something else, isn't he?
I guess the apple doesn't
fall too far from the tree.
It's crazy!
Who knew that young Buck Sanji
was Jeremiah Double Six's prince?
How insolent!
He didn't even mention it to me once!
It pisses me off.
As a result of that whole cake incident,
And Jarema's been booted
from the world's government.
My, my, Straw Boy and Sanji Boy.
It's just as I expected, though.
They're becoming the center of
attention in the Great Pirate Era.
I'm excited to see where this goes.
Anyway, our officers are running
kind of late, aren't they?
Hopefully they didn't get held
up too bad on their way here.
No kidding.
By the way, Sabo, what you got
going on over there, honey pie?
Let me guess,
your face is cramping because you keep
smiling every time you
think of the Luffy news,
right?
You boob!
Hello, Lindbergh here!
You guys are really
late, what's the hold-up?
Oh, hey, Sabo!
We are almost there!
We ran into some trouble!
Do you guys mind if we're a bit late?
No problem, just stay safe.
Oh, I am absolutely thrilled!
All of the Revolutionary Army's best
will be here in the flesh at long last!
I can't believe I'll
get to chat with Morley!
Oh, who cares?
It's all about Betty!
Sabo, we've wasted enough time.
We should hold our meeting now.
We might as well solidify
our plan before they arrive.
Looks like you're up, Mr.
Second-in-Command. Yep.
With the reverie just around the
corner, we'll finally take action.
We will be declaring war.
On the Celestial Dragons.
The Revolutionary Army.
They're all so powerful.
I can't believe it!
Why are four top officers
needed to defend one town?
Jeez, this guy is so dense.
He only wants you for
your body, obviously.
Yuck, no thank you!
Hey, I checked with Zeff like you asked.
Can we do this now, Betty?
Your power list is stopless, eh?
Why is no one answering the question?
And what is he mumbling about, anyway?
I've had enough of you.
Did this guy just snap?
Hey, you pieces of
crap. You're gonna help?
Will you die or will you fight?
It's time to choose your destiny!
Is playing hero someone else's job?!
Are you just going to cower in fear?!
I'm here!
Momo!
Do you really think a couple
of sticks are gonna stop us?
You guys are cracking me up!
What is this, a peasant uprising?
I'm not sure why, but all of a sudden I
feel this huge surge of power inside me.
Yeah, let's force these pirates to leave.
We should fight and
protect our kingdom. Yeah!
That's the stuff.
You're feeling the raw power
of Betty's pump-pump fruit.
With a mere wave of her banner, she
can call forth the strength within you.
Betty is a flag bearer of freedom!
Now, let's go!
Well, I guess they want to see
what bullets do to their bodies.
They don't know what they're in for.
Hey, Lin, Karasu, go and back them up!
As you wish!
Now freeze!
Cool shooter!
That's freezing!
My gun got all iced up!
How dare you attack those you bastards!
Don't back down!
Rip them to shreds!
Disarmed at me.
The frickin' bird's door door! Come back!
It's all up to you!
Seize your own fate!
Now go!
Run in hell!
What is this?
Why are they fired up?
You jerk!
This is for the milk!
I'm taking it back!
We're out of here.
We'll make you pay for this!
Peachbeard, 52 million berries, huh?
Master Blackbeard will avenge
me, then you'll be sorry.
I hate to break it to you, but he
doesn't give a crap about his thugs.
Man, what's your problem?
You're annoying.
Agreed.
Listen up, you pathetic,
yellow-bellied, weak, sad sacks.
All you gotta do is give
them to the world government.
And that sweet bounty will be yours.
That would be a total
of 52 million berries.
So, make sure to use it wisely.
Here, I want you to have this.
You can use it to contact
the Revolutionary Army.
You all made me proud today.
Just hit us up anytime when the
week stand up for themselves.
We will always be close
behind and ready to fight
I can't thank you enough for this!
We'll never forget what you've done!
Say, what exactly is the reason we're
meeting up with everyone anyway?
We'll be picking a fight
with the Celestial Dragons.
Oh, now that sounds like
a good time! Heck yeah!
Oh, one thing, Karasu.
You need to turn off your loudspeaker!
Sorry. Forgot.
Only two days remain until
the reverie and the schemes
of players from around the
world begin to intertwine.
Okay, roger that.
I have an update for you. Sabo?
They'll be here soon.
Alright.
Let's do this.
What is this crap?
I've seen this stupid face before.
This is the same guy who screwed
over my entire smile production.
How in the hell did he manage
to take down that old bag?
It says he won.
What the hell?
When did I lose?
And to whom?
I think I know who wrote
this slanderous article.
Mama, I do too.
I'll have to teach Morgan's a lesson,
but Straw Hat, you're first!
I'll be coming for you.
The fifth Emperor now—that
title doesn't fit you at all!
Looks
like I'll be seeing you soon. Luffy.
Luffy
So what if it got lower?
We can't do anything.
You'll get up there again, Loopy.
You know I got your back.
We'll get it even higher.
You hungry?
I'll make lunch.
Uh, just a moment.
Look, I believe you missed
a few zeros here, Luffy.
Unreal.
Your bounty's not 150 million.
It's 1.5 billion!
While the rest of the world
looks towards the reverie,
the Straw Hats embark to the land of Wano.